<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Xenophanes Musings</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Xenophanes Musings</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 12:45:50 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Beginning</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/new-beginning/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 May 2025 12:45:50 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/new-beginning/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;beginning-of-xenophanes-musings&#34;&gt;Beginning of Xenophanes musings&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am restarting my old way of blogging with more quantity, with the right quality efforts. i have decided to move all my writings from my beehiiv newsletter to a personal blogging site.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-journey-of-writing&#34;&gt;My journey of writing:&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Looking back, I started to write from the year 2020 with Hugo static site generator hosted in Netlify. &lt;a href=&#34;https://pwnl0rd.netlify.app/&#34;&gt;https://pwnl0rd.netlify.app/&lt;/a&gt; I was not a consistent writer back then and i used to tinker with computer systems. Now i am a theorist, i think before i do, i ask questions against the assumptions that are held. As a habit, i read books for 30 mins daily and i write connecting between security and the book i read. From late 2023, i consistently started to write one blog post per month. Now, I want to do more. I have decided to write more and write when i want to write.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Being Pragmatic</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/being-pragmatic/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 May 2025 17:26:56 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/being-pragmatic/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was been a pragmatic guy when i started the cybersecurity journey. Pragmatic is doing things practically without any idea or principle behind it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Being pragmatic is just doing and not thinking about how or why we are doing it, or not thinking about the method. A method is important as it shows the way to derive objective knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;knowledge-creation&#34;&gt;Knowledge Creation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To obtain knowledge, there are three ways: inductive reasoning, empirical observation, and scientific method.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
